[
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is an example of big data utilized in action today?",
    "answers": ["Social Media"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What reasoning was given for the following: why is the \"data storage to price ratio\" relevant to big data?",
    "answers": [
      "Lower prices mean larger storage becomes easier to access for everyone, creating bigger amounts of data for client-facing services to work with."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the best description of personalized marketing enabled by big data?",
    "answers": [
      "Being able to use personalized data from every single customer for personalized marketing needs."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Of the following, which is an example of personalized marketing related with big data?",
    "answers": [
      "Google ordering ads to show items based on recent and past search results."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the workflow for working with big data?",
    "answers": ["Big Data -> Better Models -> Higher Precision"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is the most compelling reason why mobile advertising is related to big data?",
    "answers": [
      "Mobile advertising benefits from data integration with location which requires big data."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the three types of diverse data sources?",
    "answers": ["Machine Data, Organizational Data, and People"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is an example of machine data?",
    "answers": ["Weather station sensor output."]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is an example of organizational data?",
    "answers": ["Disease data from Center for Disease Control."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Of the three data sources, which is the hardest to implement and streamline into a model?",
    "answers": ["People"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following summarizes the process of using data streams?",
    "answers": ["Integration -> Personalization -> Precision"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Where does the real value of big data often come from?",
    "answers": [
      "Combining streams of data and analyzing them for new insights."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What does it mean for a device to be \"smart\"?",
    "answers": ["Collect data and services autonomously."]
  },
  {
    "question": "What does the term \"in situ\" mean in the context of big data?",
    "answers": ["Bringing the computation to the location of the data."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following are reasons mentioned for why data generated by people are hard to process? Choose all that apply.",
    "answers": [
      "The velocity of the data is very high.",
      "Skilled people to analyze the data are hard to come by.",
      "Very unstructured data."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the purpose of retrieval and storage; pre-processing; and analysis in order to convert multiple data sources into valuable data?",
    "answers": ["To allow scalable analytical solutions to big data."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following are benefits of organization-generated data? Choose all that apply.",
    "answers": [
      "Customer Satisfaction",
      "Better Profit Margins",
      "Higher Sales",
      "Improved Safety"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What are data silos and why are they bad?",
    "answers": [
      "Data produced from an organization that is spread out. Bad because it creates unsynchronized and invisible data."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following are benefits of data integration? Choose all that apply.",
    "answers": [
      "Adds value to big data.",
      "Reduce data complexity.",
      "Unify your data system.",
      "Increase data availability.",
      "Increase data collaboration."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following are parts of the 5 P's of data science and what is the additional P introduced in the slides?",
    "answers": [
      "Programmability",
      "Process",
      "Platforms",
      "Purpose",
      "People",
      "Product"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following are part of the four main categories to acquire, access, and retrieve data?",
    "answers": [
      "Remote Data",
      "Text Files",
      "NoSQL Storage",
      "Traditional Databases"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the steps required for data analysis?",
    "answers": ["Select Technique, Build Model, Evaluate"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Of the following, which is a technique mentioned in the videos for building a model?",
    "answers": ["Analysis"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the first step in finding a right problem to tackle in data science?",
    "answers": ["Define the Problem"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the first step in determining a big data strategy?",
    "answers": ["Business Objectives"]
  },
  {
    "question": "According to Ilkay, why is exploring data crucial to better modeling? Data exploration... <complete the sentence>",
    "answers": [
      "leads to data understanding which allows an informed analysis of the data."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Why is data science mainly about teamwork?",
    "answers": [
      "Data science requires a variety of expertise in different fields."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the ways to address data quality issues?",
    "answers": [
      "Generate best estimates for invalid values.",
      "Merge duplicate records.",
      "Remove outliers.",
      "Remove data with missing values."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is done to the data in the preparation stage?",
    "answers": ["Understand Nature of Data and Preliminary Analysis."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is the best description of why it is important to learn about the foundations for big data?",
    "answers": [
      "Foundations allow for the understanding of practical concepts in Hadoop."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the benefit of a commodity cluster?",
    "answers": ["Cost Effective"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is a way to enable fault tolerance?",
    "answers": ["Redundant Data Storage", "Data-Parallel Job Restart"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the specific benefit(s) to a distributed file system?",
    "answers": ["Data Scalability", "High Concurrency", "High Fault Tolerance"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following are general requirements for a programming language in order to support big data models?",
    "answers": ["Handle Fault Tolerance", "Support Big Data Operations"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Run wordcount on the alice.txt file. This can be done by using hadoop commands. Remember to place the file into the HDFS. How many times does the word Cheshire occur? (Do not include the word 'Cheshire with an apostrophe. The string -->'Cheshire<-- does not count) Enter a number:",
    "answers": ["6"]
  },
  {
    "question": "The set of example MapReduce applications includes wordmedian, which computes the median length of words in a text file. If you run wordmedian using alice.txt as input, what is the median word length? Note that wordmedian prints the median length to the terminal at the end of the MapReduce job; the output file does not contain the median length. Enter a number:",
    "answers": ["4"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What does IaaS provide?",
    "answers": ["Computing Environment"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What does PaaS provide?",
    "answers": ["Computing Environment"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What does SaaS provide?",
    "answers": ["Software On-Demand"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the two key components of HDFS and what are they used for?",
    "answers": ["NameNode for metadata and DataNode for block storage."]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the job of the NameNode?",
    "answers": ["Coordinate operations and assigns tasks to Data Nodes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the order of the three steps to Map Reduce?",
    "answers": ["Map -> Shuffle and Sort -> Reduce"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is a benefit of using pre-built Hadoop images?",
    "answers": ["Quick prototyping, deploying, and validating of projects."]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is an example of open-source tools built for Hadoop and what does it do?",
    "answers": ["Giraph, for processing large-scale graphs."]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the difference between low level interfaces and high level interfaces?",
    "answers": [
      "Low level deals with storage and scheduling while high level deals with interactivity."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following are problems to look out for when integrating your project with Hadoop?",
    "answers": ["Random Data Access", "Infrastructure Replacement"]
  },
  {
    "question": "As covered in the slides, which of the following are the major goals of Hadoop?",
    "answers": [
      "Enable Scalability",
      "Handle Fault Tolerance",
      "Facilitate a Shared Environment",
      "Provide Value for Data"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the purpose of YARN?",
    "answers": [
      "Allows various applications to run on the same Hadoop cluster."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the two main components for a data computation framework that were described in the slides?",
    "answers": ["Resource Manager and Node Manager"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Amazon has been collecting review data for a particular product. They have realized that almost 90% of the reviews were mostly a 5/5 rating. However, of the 90%, they realized that 50% of them were customers who did not have proof of purchase or customers who did not post serious reviews about the product. Of the following, which is true about the review data collected in this situation?",
    "answers": ["Low Veracity"]
  },
  {
    "question": "As mentioned in the slides, what are the challenges to data with a high valence?",
    "answers": ["Difficult to Integrate"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following are the 6 V's in big data?",
    "answers": ["Veracity", "Valence", "Variety", "Velocity", "Value", "Volume"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the veracity of big data?",
    "answers": ["The abnormality or uncertainties of data."]
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the challenges of data with high variety?",
    "answers": ["Hard to integrate."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is the best way to describe why it is crucial to process data in real-time?",
    "answers": ["Prevents missed opportunities."]
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the challenges with big data that has high volume?",
    "answers": ["Cost, Scalability, and Performance"]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Questions 1-3 pertain to the video lecture “Exploring the Relational Data Model of CSV”) What is the approximate population of La Paz county in the state of Arizona for the CENSUS2010POP (column H)? (Choose the best answer.)",
    "answers": ["20000"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What county in the state of Wyoming has the smallest estimated population?",
    "answers": ["Niobrara"]
  },
  {
    "question": "At 2:45 of the video, the Instructor creates a filter for all of the counties in California with a population greater than 1,000,000. However, included in the results is the entire state of California. This anomalous value might skew our analysis if, for example, we wanted to compute the average population of these results. What additional filter might work to resolve this problem?",
    "answers": [
      "Add a filter to detect and remove results which do not include the word “County” in column G."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Questions 4 and 5 pertain to the video \"Exploring Sensor Data\") How often (in seconds) do the R5 measurements occur?",
    "answers": ["60"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the field for rain accumulation?",
    "answers": ["Rc"]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Questions 6 and 7 pertain to the video lecture \"Exploring the Array Data Model of an Image\") What is the (Red, Green, Blue) pixel value for location 500, 2000?",
    "answers": ["(163, 118, 79)"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is this value likely to be land or ocean?",
    "answers": ["Land"]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Questions 8 and 9 pertain to the video lecture \"Exploring the Semistructured Data Model of JSON\") Given a tweet, what path would you most likely enter to obtain a count of the number of followers for a user?",
    "answers": ["user/followers_count"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following fields are nested within the ‘entities’ field (select all that apply)?",
    "answers": ["user_mentions", "urls", "symbols"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is a possible pitfall of utilizing Excel as a way to manipulate small databases?",
    "answers": [
      "Excel does not enforce many principles of relational data models."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What does the term “atomic” mean in the context of relational databases?",
    "answers": ["One unit of information that cannot be decomposed."]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Pareto-Optimality problem?",
    "answers": [
      "Find the best possible path given two or more optimization criteria where neither constraint can be fully optimized simultaneously."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What constitutes a community within a graph?",
    "answers": [
      "A dense amount of edge connections between nodes in a community and a few connections across communities."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Why are trees useful for semi-structured data such as XML and JSON?",
    "answers": [
      "Trees take advantage of the parent-child relationship of the data for easy navigation."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the general purpose of modeling data as vectors?",
    "answers": ["Results can be ordered by similarity using vector projection."]
  },
  {
    "question": "For the following questions 7, 8, and 9, suppose a registration website creates data with the following fields for each person registered (note: if the user does not input a value, NULL is stored instead): Name, Date, Address, and Account Number. Suppose we collect data month by month. Each month, we would have a batch of data containing the fields listed above. At the end of the year, we want to summarize our registrant activities for the entire year, so we would remove redundancies in our data by removing any records with duplicate account numbers from month to month. What type of operation do we use in this scenario?",
    "answers": ["Union"]
  },
  {
    "question": "From the information given in question 7, what are the constraints, if any, which we have placed on the Account Number field for the end of year collection?",
    "answers": ["Account Number should be unique."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Suppose 100 people signup for our system and of the 100 people, 60 of them did not input an address. The system lists the values as NULL for these empty entries in the address field. Would this situation still have structure for our data?",
    "answers": [
      "Yes the data has structure because we have placed a structural constraint on the data, thus the data will always have the originally defined structure."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is true between data modeling and the formatting of the data?",
    "answers": [
      "The data does not necessarily need to be formatted in a way that represents the data model. Just so long as it can be extrapolated."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is streaming?",
    "answers": [
      "Utilizing real time data to compute and change the state of an application continuously."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Of the following, what best describes the properties of working with streaming data?",
    "answers": [
      "Small time windows for working with data.",
      "Always unbounded in sequence, in other words, data is not guaranteed to be in order.",
      "Data manipulation is near real time."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is a characteristic of streaming data?",
    "answers": [
      "The data is unbounded in size and the size determines the time and space of processing the data."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of algorithm is required for analyzing streaming data?",
    "answers": ["Fast and Simple"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is lambda architecture?",
    "answers": [
      "A method to process streaming data by utilizing batch processing and real time processing."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Of the following, which best represents the challenge regarding the size and frequency of data?",
    "answers": ["The size and frequency of the streaming data may be sporadic."]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the difference between data lakes and data warehouses?",
    "answers": [
      "Data lakes house raw data while data warehouses contain pre-formatted data."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is schema-on-read?",
    "answers": [
      "Data is stored as raw data until it is read by an application where the application assigns structure."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "The desired characteristics of a BDMS include (select all that apply):",
    "answers": [
      "Continuous data ingestion",
      "Support for common “Big Data” data types",
      "A flexible semi-structured data model",
      "A full query language"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Fill in the blank with the best answer: CAP theorem states that _________ all at once within a distributed computer system?",
    "answers": [
      "it is impossible to have consistency, availability, and partition tolerance"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the purpose of the acronym BASE?",
    "answers": ["To overcome CAP theorem."]
  },
  {
    "question": "What are ziplists in Redis?",
    "answers": [
      "A compressed list that is stored within the value of the database."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is one of the main features of Aerospike?",
    "answers": ["Support for geospatial data storage and geospatial queries."]
  },
  {
    "question": "What database would be best suited for the following scenario: An app development company is trying to implement a cloud based storage system for their new map-based app. The cloud will manage the longitude and latitude of the data in order to track user location.",
    "answers": ["Aerospike"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What database would be best suited for the following scenario: A big wholesale company is trying to implement a search engine for their products.",
    "answers": ["Solr"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following data types are supported by Redis? (select all that apply)",
    "answers": ["Sorted Sets", "Hashes", "Strings", "Lists"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What does it mean for a query language to be declarative?",
    "answers": ["The language specifies what data to obtain."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Use the following table named \"user_table\" to answer the next 2 problems. userId username email 1 admin admin@corporate.moe 2 h4xor 1337@rawr.cte How would you go about querying the entire username column (however many)?",
    "answers": ["SELECT username FROM user_table"]
  },
  {
    "question": "How would you go about querying the entire database table (please refer to question 2's table)?",
    "answers": ["SELECT * FROM user_table"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the global indexing table?",
    "answers": [
      "An index table in order to keep track of a given data type that might exist within multiple machines."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the three computing steps of a semi-join?",
    "answers": ["Project, Ship, Reduce"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the purpose of a semi-join?",
    "answers": [
      "Increase the efficiency of sending data across multiple machines."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is a subquery?",
    "answers": ["A query statement within another query."]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is a correlated subquery?",
    "answers": [
      "A type of query that contains a subquery that requires information from a query one level up."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the purpose of GROUP BY queries?",
    "answers": [
      "Required before you can use functions like AVG, SUM, MIN, MAX, COUNT."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Consider the following generic statement for questions 10-12: db.<collection>.find(<query filter>, <projection>).<cursor modifier> Which part of the statement would reflect that of the FROM statement in SQL as illustrated in the lecture?",
    "answers": ["<collection>"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which part of the statement would reflect that of the SELECT statement in SQL as illustrated in the lecture?",
    "answers": ["<projection>"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which part of the statement would reflect that of the WHERE statement in SQL as illustrated in the lecture?",
    "answers": ["<query filter>"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A sample part of the data structure is as follows: { _id:1, userIndex: 10, email: “arealeamil@notreallu.asd\", retainRate:2} What would be the most likely statement that we would need to grab email info for user indexes greater than 24?",
    "answers": ["db.email.find({userIndex:{$gt:24}}, {email:1, _id:0})"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What does it mean to have a _id:0 within our query statement?",
    "answers": ["Tell MongoDB not to return a document id."]
  },
  {
    "question": "This quiz encompasses data and content from Week 1 and 2, so we recommend reviewing that material from last week for this quiz as well. What is the highest level that the team has reached in gameclicks? (Hint: use the MAX operation in postgres).",
    "answers": ["8"]
  },
  {
    "question": "How many user id's (repeats allowed) have reached the highest level as found in the previous question? (Hint: For postgres: you may either use two queries or use a sub-query).",
    "answers": ["51294"]
  },
  {
    "question": "How many user id’s (repeats allowed) reached the highest level in game-clicks and also clicked the highest costing price in buy-clicks? Hint: Refer to question 4 for ideas.",
    "answers": ["32747"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What does the following line of code do in postgres? SELECT count(userid) FROM (SELECT buyclicks.userId, teamLevel, price FROM buyclicks JOIN gameclicks on buyclicks.userId = gameclicks.userId) temp WHERE price=3 and teamLevel=5;",
    "answers": [
      "Finds the total number of user ids (repeats allowed) in buy-clicks that have bought items with prices worth $3 and was in a team with level 5 at some point in time."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "In the MongoDB data set, what is the username of the twitter account who has a tweet_followers_count of exactly 8973882?",
    "answers": ["FIFAcom"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the main problem with big data information integration?",
    "answers": ["Many sources"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What would be the two possible solutions associated with \"big data\" information integration as mentioned in lecture? (Choose 2)",
    "answers": ["Pay-as-you-go Model", "Probabilistic Schema Mapping"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What are mediated schemas?",
    "answers": ["Schema created from integrating two or more schemas."]
  },
  {
    "question": "In attribute grouping, how would one evaluate if two attributes should go together? (Choose 2)",
    "answers": [
      "Similarity of Attributes",
      "Probability of Two Attributes Co-occurring"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is a data item?",
    "answers": ["Data that represents an aspect of a real-world entity."]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is data fusion?",
    "answers": ["Extracting the true value of a data item."]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is a potential problem of having too many data sources as mentioned in lecture?",
    "answers": ["Too many data values."]
  },
  {
    "question": "What do we mean when we say \"the true value of a data item\"?",
    "answers": [
      "Extrapolated data from a data item that represents the worth of that item."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is a potential method to deal with too many data sources as mentioned in lecture?",
    "answers": ["Compare and weigh each source by their trustworthiness."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the queries below will return the average population of the counties in Georgia (be careful not to include the population of the state of Georgia itself)?",
    "answers": [
      "source=\"census.csv\" CTYNAME != \"Georgia\" STNAME=\"Georgia\" | stats mean(CENSUS2010POP)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average population of the counties in the state of Georgia (be careful not to include the population of the state of Georgia itself)?",
    "answers": ["60928.635220"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Of the options below, which query allows you to find the state with the most counties?",
    "answers": [
      "source=\"census.csv\" | stats count by STNAME | sort count desc"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What state contains the most counties?",
    "answers": ["Texas"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Of the options below, which query allows you to find the most populated counties in the state of Texas?",
    "answers": ["Both"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the most populated county in the state of Texas?",
    "answers": ["Harris"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is data-parallelism as defined in lecture?",
    "answers": [
      "Running the same function simultaneously for the partitions of a data set on multiple cores."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Of the following, which procedure best generalizes big data procedures such as (but not limited to) the map reduce process?",
    "answers": ["split->do->merge"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the three layers for the Hadoop Ecosystem? (Choose 3)",
    "answers": [
      "Coordination and Workflow Management",
      "Data Integration and Processing",
      "Data Management and Storage"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the 5 key points in order to categorize big data systems?",
    "answers": [
      "Execution model, Latency, Scalability, Programming Language, Fault Tolerance"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the lambda architecture as shown in lecture?",
    "answers": ["A type of hybrid data processing architecture."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following scenarios is NOT an aggregation operation?",
    "answers": ["Removing undefined values."]
  },
  {
    "question": "What usually happens to data when aggregated as mentioned in lecture?",
    "answers": ["Data becomes smaller."]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is K-means clustering?",
    "answers": ["Group samples into k clusters."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Why is Hadoop not a good platform for machine learning as mentioned in lecture? (Choose 4)",
    "answers": [
      "No interactive shell and streaming.",
      "Bottleneck using HDFS.",
      "Map and Reduce Based Computation.",
      "Java support only."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the layers (parts) of Spark? (Choose 5)",
    "answers": ["Spark Core", "MLlib", "Graphx", "Spark Streaming", "SparkSQL"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is in-memory processing?",
    "answers": ["Writing data to memory between pipeline steps."]
  },
  {
    "question": "What does the following line of code do? words = lines.flatMap(lambda line: line.split(“ “))",
    "answers": ["Each line in the document is split up into words."]
  },
  {
    "question": "What does the following line of code imply about the state of partitions before the action is performed? words = lines.flatMap(lambda line: line.split(“ “))",
    "answers": ["Each Spark partition corresponds to a line in the document."]
  },
  {
    "question": "When the following command is executed, where is the file written and how can it be accessed? counts.coalesce(1).saveAsTextFile(‘hdfs:/user/cloudera/wordcount/outputDir’)",
    "answers": ["HDFS and through the “hadoop fs” command."]
  },
  {
    "question": "What does the number one (1) allow us to do in the following line of code? tuples = words.map(lambda word: (word,1))",
    "answers": [
      "Treat each word with a weight of one during the counting process."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which part of SPARK is in charge of creating RDDs?",
    "answers": ["Driver Program"]
  },
  {
    "question": "How does lazy evaluation work in Spark?",
    "answers": ["Transformations are not executed until the action stage."]
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the consequences of lazy evaluation as mentioned in lecture?",
    "answers": ["Errors sometimes do not show up until the action stage."]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is a wide transformation?",
    "answers": [
      "A transformation that requires data shuffling across node partitions."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Where does the data for each worker node get sent to after a collect function is called?",
    "answers": ["Spark Context"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What are DataFrames?",
    "answers": ["A column like data format that can be read by Spark SQL."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Can RDD's be converted into DataFrames directly without manipulation?",
    "answers": ["No: lines have to be converted into row."]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the function of Spark SQL as mentioned in lecture? (Choose 3)",
    "answers": [
      "Enables relational queries on Spark.",
      "Connect to variety of databases.",
      "Efficient data manipulation using SQL like structure."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is a triplet in GraphX?",
    "answers": ["A type of data to contain edge info."]
  },
  {
    "question": "What does the following filter line of code do? df.filter(df[“teamlevel”] > 1)",
    "answers": ["Filter each row to show only team levels larger than 1."]
  },
  {
    "question": "What does the following do? df.select(“userid”, “teamlevel”).show(5)",
    "answers": [
      "Select the columns named “userid” and “teamlevel” and display first 5 rows."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What does the following code do? window(\"time\", \"10 seconds\")",
    "answers": ["Creates a 10 second window, using column \"time\" timestamps."]
  },
  {
    "question": "query = ( windowed_data .writeStream .outputMode(\"update\") .trigger(processingTime=\"10 seconds\") .foreachBatch(lambda batch_df, epoch_id: batch_df.show(truncate=False)) .start() ) In the previous code, Which method initiates the retrieval of streaming data?",
    "answers": ["start()"]
  },
  {
    "question": "How many tweets have location not null?",
    "answers": ["6973"]
  },
  {
    "question": "How many people have more followers than friends? (Hint : use this.user instead of user).",
    "answers": ["5809"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Perform a query that returns the text of tweets which have the string \"http://\". Which of the following substrings do NOT occur in the results? (Choose all that apply)",
    "answers": ["@DundalkFC", "@Infosmessi_"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Query: Return all the tweets which contain text \"England\" but not \"UEFA\". In these results the string “Euro 2016” appears in...",
    "answers": ["2 tweets"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Query: Get all the tweets from the location \"Ireland\" which also contain the string \"UEFA\". In this result the user with the highest friends count is...",
    "answers": ["ProfitwatchInfo"]
  },
  {
    "question": "How many different countries are mentioned in at least one tweet?",
    "answers": ["44"]
  },
  {
    "question": "How many times is any country mentioned in a tweet?",
    "answers": ["397"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the three countries with the highest mentioned count",
    "answers": ["Norway, Nigeria, France"]
  },
  {
    "question": "How many times was France mentioned in a tweet?",
    "answers": ["42"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which country was mentioned most: Kenya, Wales, or Netherlands?",
    "answers": ["Wales"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average number of times a country is mentioned? (Round to the nearest integer)",
    "answers": ["9"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is NOT machine learning?",
    "answers": ["Explicit, step-by-step programming"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is NOT a category of machine learning?",
    "answers": ["Algorithm Prediction"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which categories of machine learning techniques are supervised?",
    "answers": ["classification and regression"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In unsupervised approaches,",
    "answers": ["the target is unknown or unavailable."]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sequence of the steps in the machine learning process?",
    "answers": ["Acquire -> Prepare -> Analyze -> Act -> Report"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Are the steps in the machine learning process apply-once or iterative?",
    "answers": ["Iterative"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Phase 2 of CRISP-DM is Data Understanding. In this phase,",
    "answers": [
      "we acquire as well as explore the data that is related to the problem."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the main difference between KNIME and Spark MLlib?",
    "answers": [
      "KNIME is a graphical user interface-based machine learning tool, while Spark MLlib provides a programming-based distributed platform for scalable machine learning algorithms."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of these statements is true about samples and variables?",
    "answers": ["All of these statements are true."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Other names for 'variable' are",
    "answers": ["feature, column, attribute"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the purpose of exploring data?",
    "answers": ["To gain a better understanding of your data."]
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the two main categories of techniques for exploring data? Choose two.",
    "answers": ["Visualization", "Summary statistics"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following are NOT examples of summary statistics?",
    "answers": ["data sources, data locations"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the two measures for measuring shape as mentioned in the lecture? Choose two.",
    "answers": ["Skewness", "Kurtosis"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following would NOT be a good reason to use a box plot?",
    "answers": ["To show correlations between two variables."]
  },
  {
    "question": "All of the following are true about data visualization EXCEPT",
    "answers": [
      "Is more important than summary statistics for data exploration"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the maximum of the average wind speed measurements at 9am (to 2 decimal places)?",
    "answers": ["23.56"]
  },
  {
    "question": "How many rows containing rain accumulation at 9am measurements have missing values?",
    "answers": ["6"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the correlation between the relative humidity at 9am and at 3pm (to 2 decimal places, and without removing or imputing missing values)?",
    "answers": ["0.88"]
  },
  {
    "question": "If the histogram for air temperature at 9am has 50 bins, what is the number of elements in the bin with the most elements (without removing or imputing missing values)?",
    "answers": ["57"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the approximate maximum max_wind_direction_9am when the maximum max_wind_speed_9am occurs?",
    "answers": ["70"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is NOT a data quality issue?",
    "answers": ["Scaled data"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Imputing missing data means to",
    "answers": ["replace missing values with something reasonable."]
  },
  {
    "question": "A data sample with values that are considerably different than the rest of the other data samples in the dataset is called an/a _____________.",
    "answers": ["Outlier"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which one of the following examples illustrates the use of domain knowledge to address a data quality issue?",
    "answers": ["Merge duplicate records while retaining relevant data"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is NOT an example of feature selection?",
    "answers": ["Replacing a missing value with the variable mean."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which one of the following is the best feature set for your analysis?",
    "answers": [
      "Feature set with the smallest set of features that best capture the characteristics of the data for the intended application"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "The mean value and the standard deviation of a zero-normalized feature are",
    "answers": ["mean = 0 and standard deviation = 1"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is NOT true about PCA?",
    "answers": [
      "PCA is a dimensionality reduction technique that removes a feature that is very correlated with another feature."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "If we remove all missing values from the data, how many air pressure at 9am measurements have values between 911.736 and 914.67?",
    "answers": ["77"]
  },
  {
    "question": "If we impute the missing values with the minimum value, how many air temperature at 9am measurements are less than 42.292?",
    "answers": ["28"]
  },
  {
    "question": "How many samples have missing values for air_pressure_9am?",
    "answers": ["3"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which column in the weather dataset has the most number of missing values?",
    "answers": ["rain_accumulation_9am"]
  },
  {
    "question": "When we remove all the missing values from the dataset, the number of rows is 1064, yet the variable with most missing values has 1089 rows. Why did the number of rows decrease so much?",
    "answers": [
      "Because the missing values in each column are not necessarily in the same row"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is a TRUE statement about classification?",
    "answers": ["Classification is a supervised task."]
  },
  {
    "question": "In which phase are model parameters adjusted?",
    "answers": ["Training phase"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which classification algorithm uses a probabilistic approach?",
    "answers": ["naive bayes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What does the 'k' stand for in k-nearest-neighbors?",
    "answers": [
      "the number of nearest neighbors to consider in classifying a sample"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "During construction of a decision tree, there are several criteria that can be used to determine when a node should no longer be split into subsets. Which one of the following is NOT applicable?",
    "answers": ["The value of the Gini index reaches a maximum threshold."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which statement is true of tree induction?",
    "answers": ["All of these statements are true of tree induction."]
  },
  {
    "question": "What does 'naive' mean in Naive Bayes?",
    "answers": [
      "The model assumes that the input features are statistically independent of one another. The 'naïve' in the name of classifier comes from this naïve assumption."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "The feature independence assumption in Naive Bayes simplifies the classification problem by",
    "answers": [
      "allowing the probability of each feature given the class to be estimated individually."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "KNIME: In configuring the Numeric Binner node, what would happen if the definition for the humidity_low bin is changed from ] -infinity ... 25.0 [ to ] -infinity ... 25.0 ] (i.e., the last bracket is changed from [ to ] ?",
    "answers": [
      "The definition for the humidity_low bin would change from excluding 25.0 to including 25.0"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "KNIME: Considering the Numeric Binner node again, what would happen if the “Append new column” box is not checked?",
    "answers": [
      "The relative_humidity_3pm variable will become a categorical variable"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "KNIME: How many samples had a missing value for air_temp_9am before missing values were addressed?",
    "answers": ["5"]
  },
  {
    "question": "KNIME: How many samples were placed in the test set after the dataset was partitioned into training and test sets?",
    "answers": ["213"]
  },
  {
    "question": "KNIME: What are the target and predicted class labels for the first sample in the test set?",
    "answers": ["Both are humidity_not_low"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Spark: What values are in the number column?",
    "answers": ["Integer values starting at 0"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Spark: With the original dataset split into 80% for training and 20% for test, how many of the first 20 samples from the test set were correctly classified?",
    "answers": ["16"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Spark: If we split the data using 70% for training data and 30% for test data, how many samples would the training set have (using seed 13234)?",
    "answers": ["731"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A model that generalizes well means that",
    "answers": ["The model performs well on data not used in training."]
  },
  {
    "question": "What indicates that the model is overfitting?",
    "answers": ["Low training error and high generalization error"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which method is used to avoid overfitting in decision trees?",
    "answers": ["Pre-pruning and post-pruning"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following best describes a way to create and use a validation set to avoid overfitting?",
    "answers": ["All of these"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following statements is NOT correct?",
    "answers": [
      "The test set is used for model selection to avoid overfitting."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How is the accuracy rate calculated?",
    "answers": [
      "Divide the number of correct predictions by the total number of predictions"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which evaluation metrics are commonly used for evaluating the performance of a classification model when there is a class imbalance problem?",
    "answers": ["precision and recall"]
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you determine the classifier accuracy from the confusion matrix?",
    "answers": [
      "Divide the sum of the diagonal values in the confusion matrix by the total number of samples."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "KNIME: In the confusion matrix as viewed in the Scorer node, low_humidity_day is:",
    "answers": ["the target class label"]
  },
  {
    "question": "KNIME: In the confusion matrix, what is the difference between low_humidity_day and Prediction(low_humidity_day)?",
    "answers": [
      "low_humidity_day is the target class label, and Prediction(low_humidity_day) is the predicted class label"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "KNIME: In the Table View of the Interactive Table, each row is color-coded. Red specifies:",
    "answers": [
      "that the target class label for the sample is humidity_not_low"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "KNIME: To change the colors used to color-code each sample in the Table View of the Interactive Table node:",
    "answers": ["change the color settings in the Color Manager node"]
  },
  {
    "question": "KNIME: In the Table View of the Interactive Table, the values in RowID are not consecutive because:",
    "answers": [
      "the RowID values are from the original dataset, and only the test samples are displayed here"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Spark: To get the error rate for the decision tree model, use the following code:",
    "answers": ["1 print (\"Error = %g \" % (1.0 - accuracy))"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Spark: To print out the accuracy as a percentage, use the following code:",
    "answers": ["1 print (\"Accuracy = %.2g\" % (accuracy * 100))"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Spark: In the last line of code in Step 4, the confusion matrix is printed out. If the “transpose()” is removed, the confusion matrix will be displayed as:",
    "answers": ["1 2 array([[87., 19.], [28., 84.]])"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the main difference between classification and regression?",
    "answers": [
      "In classification, you're predicting a category, and in regression, you're predicting a number."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is NOT an example of regression?",
    "answers": ["Determining whether power usage will rise or fall"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In linear regression, the least squares method is used to",
    "answers": ["Determine the regression line that best fits the samples."]
  },
  {
    "question": "How does simple linear regression differ from multiple linear regression?",
    "answers": [
      "In simple linear regression, the input has only one variable. In multiple linear regression, the input has more than one variables."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "The goal of cluster analysis is",
    "answers": [
      "To segment data so that differences between samples in the same cluster are minimized and differences between samples of different clusters are maximized."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Cluster results can be used to",
    "answers": [
      "All of these choices are valid uses of the resulting clusters."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A cluster centroid is",
    "answers": ["The mean of all the samples in the cluster"]
  },
  {
    "question": "The main steps in the k-means clustering algorithm are",
    "answers": [
      "Assign each sample to the closest centroid, then calculate the new centroid."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "The goal of association analysis is",
    "answers": ["To find rules to capture associations between items or events"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In association analysis, an item set is",
    "answers": ["A transaction or set of items that occur together"]
  },
  {
    "question": "The support of an item set",
    "answers": ["Captures the frequency of that item set"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Rule confidence is used to",
    "answers": ["Prune rules by eliminating rules with low confidence"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What percentage of samples have 0 for rain_accumulation?",
    "answers": ["157812 / 158726 = 99.4%"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Why is it necessary to scale the data (Step 4)?",
    "answers": [
      "Since the values of the features are on different scales, all features need to be scaled so that no one feature dominates the clustering results."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "If we wanted to create a data subset by taking every 5th sample instead of every 10th sample, how many samples would be in that subset?",
    "answers": ["317,452"]
  },
  {
    "question": "This line of code creates a k-means model with 12 clusters: 1 kmeans = KMeans (k=12, seed=1) What is the significance of “seed=1”?",
    "answers": [
      "This sets the seed to a specific value, which is necessary to reproduce the k-means results"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Just by looking at the values for the cluster centers, which cluster contains samples with the lowest relative humidity?",
    "answers": ["Cluster 5"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What do clusters 0, 4, and 8 have in common?",
    "answers": [
      "They capture weather patterns associated with warm and dry days"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "If we perform clustering with 20 clusters (and seed = 1), which cluster appears to identify Santa Ana conditions (lowest humidity and highest wind speeds)?",
    "answers": ["Cluster 5"]
  },
  {
    "question": "We did not include the minimum wind measurements in the analysis since they are highly correlated with the average wind measurements. What is the correlation between min_wind_speed and avg_wind_speed (to two decimals)? (Compute this using one-tenth of the original dataset, and dropping all rows with missing values.)",
    "answers": ["0.97"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following content would be objects (or nodes) in a graph that represents the activity in a facebook page?",
    "answers": ["location", "post text", "comment text"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Based on the videos, which kinds of analysis might one be able to perform on a tweet graph?",
    "answers": [
      "find influencers in a twitter community",
      "extract conversation threads",
      "find interacting groups of users"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "The key reason mentioned in the video that biology applications need Big Data analytics is...",
    "answers": [
      "The integration of multiple data sources from different researchers and of different sources of information."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the Vs BEST describes the result in constant increasing in the number of edges in a graph, sometimes causing challenges in knowing when one has found \"an answer\" to one's analysis question?",
    "answers": ["Velocity"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the Vs results in increased algorithmic complexity (which can cause analyses to not be able to finish running in reasonable amounts of time)?",
    "answers": ["Volume"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the Vs results in challenges due to graphs created from varying kinds, formats, sources, and meanings of data?",
    "answers": ["Variety"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the Vs causes increased interconnectivity of a graph -- which can cause problems in analysis due to density?",
    "answers": ["Valence"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Updating a graph with a stream of posting information on facebook is an example of which of the Vs?",
    "answers": ["Velocity"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Studying Amarnath's gmail interactions over time (as gmail started to be used by more and more people) is BEST defined as an impact of which of the Vs?",
    "answers": ["Valence"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the Vs is most relevant to the kinds of graph analysis you are interested in? Tell us why in a sentence or 2. (Any response will be counted correct.)",
    "answers": [
      "The most relevant 'V' for graph analysis is 'Variety' because graph data often involves diverse and interconnected types of entities and relationships. Analyzing this variety is crucial for uncovering patterns, communities, and influence within complex networks"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A graph representing tweets would have only “one type” (e.g. label) of node.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In a network representing the world wide web nodes would likely represent:",
    "answers": ["Webpages"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In a network representing the world wide web edges (or links) would likely represent",
    "answers": ["Hyperlinks"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In an email network, which might reasonably be represented by weight on edges?",
    "answers": [
      "average number of emails sent from one user to another in a week"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A loop in a graph is where:",
    "answers": ["where there is an edge from a node to itself."]
  },
  {
    "question": "An example of a loop in a graph could occur when:",
    "answers": ["Someone emails themself"]
  },
  {
    "question": "When trying to represent a relationship between Maria and Julio who have more than one relationship to each other (e.g., tennis partner, co-worker, emergency contact) which of the following would be needed in a graph representing those relationships",
    "answers": ["Multiple edges between Maria and Julio"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In many applications paths (where we go from one node to another without repeating nodes) are more useful than walks (where we can repeat a node when going from one node to another).",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Trails (paths without repeated edges) can be interesting in which of the following problem applications?",
    "answers": ["Routing to avoid using the same bridge or road."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Suppose we have an email network where the edges of a graph represent the number of emails from one user to another. If I was going to ask if Maria had sent any emails that (either directly or through forwarding from others) reached Julio, I would ask if:",
    "answers": ["Julio’s node was reachable from Maria node"]
  },
  {
    "question": "If I want to find the diameter of a graph, I should start by finding the shortest path between each set of nodes.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the diameter of this graph?",
    "answers": ["2"]
  },
  {
    "question": "This question is about \"best paths\". To find the most discussed email in an email network, would we be looking to minimize a function or maximize a function?",
    "answers": ["Maximize"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which are the two kinds of constraints on paths discussed in the video on basic path analytics? (check 2) Hint: remember the example of Amarnath needing to get to work by taking his son to school.",
    "answers": [
      "Inclusion of nodes and/or edges",
      "Exclusion of nodes and/or edges"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What are examples of preference constraints in the Google Maps application?",
    "answers": ["Avoid roads under construction", "Avoid highways"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the statements below is true?",
    "answers": [
      "Dijsktra's algorithm is computationally inefficient (has high computational complexity)."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "In the video on \"Inclusion and Exclusion Constraints\" we learn that adding constraints can actually make our analysis job easier. For example, when we require that a given node be included on a path, which of the following impacts now make the analysis job easier? (Choose 2)",
    "answers": [
      "Reduction of the size of the graph",
      "Splitting the task into 2 independent shortest path problems"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "The example given in the lectures of when a power network loses power in large portions of its service area was an example of what?",
    "answers": ["an attack which causes disconnection of the graph"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the following graph strongly connected, weakly connected or neither?",
    "answers": ["strongly connected"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the following graph strongly connected, weakly connected or neither?",
    "answers": ["weakly connected"]
  },
  {
    "question": "If you were going to look for a node which would be most likely to be the target of an attack to disconnect a network, what would be the best characteristic to look for?",
    "answers": ["high degree nodes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the out-degree of node B?",
    "answers": ["0"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In the graph below, which node is the greatest talker?",
    "answers": ["B"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In the graph below, which nodes are the greatest communicators? (Hint: there's a tie)",
    "answers": ["A", "C"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What would we be looking for if we followed the steps below? Note: we have 2 graphs. Create a table for each graph where, for each node, you list the degree of the node. For each graph, create a histogram indicating how many nodes in that graph have a specific degree (e.g., how many nodes have degree 1? 2? etc.). Use advanced approaches (e.g. Euclidean distances) to compare these two histograms.",
    "answers": ["Similarity"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following are the three type of analytics questions asked about communities?",
    "answers": ["Static", "Evolution", "Prediction"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of community analytics question is the following? Did a community form on twitter around the 2014 World Cup in Brazil?",
    "answers": ["Evolution"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which type of community analytics question is the following? How tightly knit was the 2014 World Cup twitter community on July 13, 2014 (the day of the finals)?",
    "answers": ["Static"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the internal degree of the node indicated in the graph below?",
    "answers": ["1"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the two graphs below is more modular?",
    "answers": ["B"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following community tracking phases best describes what (usually) happens a few months after two companies merge?",
    "answers": ["Split"]
  },
  {
    "question": "An influencer in a network is defined as:",
    "answers": ["a node which can reach all other nodes quickly"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following are the 2 core “key player” problems that centrality analytics can address?",
    "answers": [
      "A set of nodes which can reach (almost) all other nodes",
      "Which nodes' removal will maximally disrupt the network"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of centrality would you want to analyze in a graph if you wanted to inject information that flows through the shortest path in a network and have it spread quickly?",
    "answers": ["Closeness"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of centrality would you want to analyze in a graph if you wanted maximize commodity flow in a network?",
    "answers": ["Between-ness"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of centrality identifies \"hubness\"?",
    "answers": ["Degree"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is a Cypher command used to combine two or more query results?",
    "answers": ["union"]
  },
  {
    "question": "For a graph network whose nodes are all of type \"MyNode\", which has both incoming and outgoing edges, and which has both root and leaf nodes, what will the following Cypher code return in a Neo4j report? match (n:MyNode)<-[r]-() return n",
    "answers": ["All nodes except root nodes."]
  },
  {
    "question": "The Cypher query language shares some commands in common with SQL.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "The following query will return a graph containing whatever loops might exist. match (n)-[r]-(n) return n, r",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Cypher pattern is used to represent a node?",
    "answers": ["()"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Neo4j is a ...",
    "answers": ["Graph database"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Cypher command launches a Neo4j database search?",
    "answers": ["MATCH"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Cypher does not include a specific command to find the shortest path in a graph network.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Cypher includes a 'diameter' command to find the longest path in a graph network.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "[NOTE: The following questions apply to the results from the \"Practicing Graph Analytics in Neo4j With Cypher\" Assignment using the dataset titled 'gene_gene_associations_50k.csv'. What is the number of nodes returned?",
    "answers": ["9656"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What’s the number of edges?",
    "answers": ["46,621"]
  },
  {
    "question": "The number of loops in the graph is:",
    "answers": ["1221"]
  },
  {
    "question": "The query match (n)-[r]->(m) where m <> n return distinct n, m, count(r) gives us",
    "answers": [
      "the count of all non loop edges between every adjacent node pair."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "The query match (n)-[r]->(m) where m <> n return distinct n, m, count(r) as myCount order by myCount desc limit 1 produces what?",
    "answers": [
      "the pair of nodes with the maximum number of multi-edges between them"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "The query match p=(n {Name:'BRCA1'})-[:AssociationType*..2]->(m) return p produces what?",
    "answers": ["The 2-neighborhood of the node whose name is ‘BRCA1’"]
  },
  {
    "question": "How many non-directed shortest paths are there between the node named ‘BRCA1’ and the node named ‘NBR1’?",
    "answers": ["9"]
  },
  {
    "question": "The top 2 nodes with the highest outdegree are:",
    "answers": ["GRB2 and TP53"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Applying the example queries provided to you, create the degree histogram for the network. How many nodes in the graph have a degree of 3?",
    "answers": ["821"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In this code snippet below from the Hands On exercise on importing data, '100L + row...' adds 100 to the value of every country ID. Which of the following statements are true regarding this decision? (Note: you may select more than one) 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 val countries: RDD[(VertexId, PlaceNode)] = sc.textFile(\"./EOADATA/country.csv\"). filter(! _.startsWith(\"#\")). map {line => val row = line split ',' (100L + row(0).toInt, Country(row(1))) }",
    "answers": [
      "Another option would have been to add 100 to the metropolis keys as they were imported, and leave the country keys as they were originally numbered.",
      "This step was needed to create unique keys between the country and the metropolis datasets."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "In the metro example, what is an in-degree in relation to a country? Hint: this was covered in Hands-On: Building a Graph",
    "answers": ["A metro area or metropolis."]
  },
  {
    "question": "In Hands On: Network Connectedness and Clustering , Antarctica is easy to identify. Why?",
    "answers": [
      "It is the green dot that that has no connections, or it is the least connected cluster."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "In the Facebook graph example, the visualization looked like broccoli. Why?",
    "answers": [
      "Social networks have communities or pockets of people who interact densely."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the in-degree of node B?",
    "answers": ["2"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In the graph below, which node is the greatest listener?",
    "answers": ["B"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the external degree of the node indicated in the graph below?",
    "answers": ["3"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following community tracking phases usually occurs when a company spins off a start-up?",
    "answers": ["Split"]
  },
  {
    "question": "The ad-click events are listed in the file ad-clicks.csv. Each advertisement that is clicked on by a user generates $0.50 of revenue. What is the total amount of revenue generated by the ad-click events?",
    "answers": ["8162"]
  },
  {
    "question": "How many different categories of advertisements are there?",
    "answers": ["9"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Let’s say electronics generates $0.75, and the other types of advertisements generate $0.40. What is the total amount of revenue?",
    "answers": ["6913"]
  },
  {
    "question": "The file buy-clicks.csv lists the in-app purchases and the price of each purchase. When a user purchases an item, the company gets 2% of the price. How much revenue does the company make from the purchases in buy-clicks.csv?",
    "answers": ["428"]
  },
  {
    "question": "How many distinct items can be purchased?",
    "answers": ["6"]
  },
  {
    "question": "How much does the most expensive item cost?",
    "answers": ["20"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the buyId of the item that is purchased the most?",
    "answers": ["2"]
  }
]
